plashporn.com 2016-12-31

# PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated, June 23, 2015.

Plashporn knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly.

### What Personal Information About Users we Gather?

1\. Information You Give Us.  
2\. Automatic Information.  
3\. E-mail Communications.

### Browser Information

We collect data regarding the users of Plashporn, including: (i) The Internet Protocol (IP) address of the user’s computer. This may or may not be associated with a particular Internet Service Provider (ISP); (ii) The referring URL, if any; (iii) The browser software identification (i.e. the brand and version of your browser software).

### Statistical Information

We log certain information concerning user’s movie browsing. For example, it is possible for us to know which movies you watch.

### Use of Personal Information

We will use the email address provided by you when you register to contact you from time to time. This may be for security reasons (so that we can check that you are who you say you are), to ask your opinion about the Website, or it may be to keep you updated on the services currently available on the Website and any changes to those services and those that we intend to launch in the future. We may also use such personal information to send you notices, on behalf of others and ourselves, regarding products and services that we think may be of interest to you. You can always unsubscribe.

### Links

We may display links to third party sites. However, we cannot control and cannot be held responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. We advise you to check their terms of use and privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

### Cookies

Plashporn collects information about you using cookies. We use this information to help us improve the efficiency and quality of our service.

### Third-Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party advertising companies to target and serve ads when you visit our Website. These third party advertisers may drop cookies onto your device when serving these adverts. Please note that we do not disclose personally identifiable information about you, which you have privately provided to Plashporn, to our advertiser partners without your consent.

If you have any questions or comments concerning this site please feel free to contact us.
